Review Exercise 14, Russian Rebellion. Russia's offensive against rebels in the
breakaway region of Chechnya is entering a new phase. On the one hand, Russian forces
are taking full control of the Russian capital, Grozny, and Moscow says the war
seems to be turning in its favor. On the other hand, the rebels could be retreating
Grozny just to fight another day, ensuring a long guerrilla war. The four-month
conflict topped the agenda today during Secretary of State Madeleine Albright's
talks with acting Russian President Vladimir Putin Albright then left for
Croatia about which we'll hear more shortly But first we turn to the world's
Nenad Shevek in Moscow Albright and Putin met for longer than planned today for
nearly three hours After their talks Albright called the meeting intense but
pleasant and offered this assessment of Russia's acting president I found him a
very well-informed person. He's obviously a Russian patriot and also someone who
seeks a normal position for Russia within the West, and he struck me as a problem
solver.